'You're running an op against
the chief of Russian intelligence
'while he's on holiday.
'which they would
consider highly provocative.
'To justify an op like this.
'Igor would have to be trading
top-grade insights with his son.
'Who's your agent in there anyway?'
'she's mikhail borodin's Russian nanny.'
200 hours of battery life.
He's got nothing to be suspicious about.
I think that's kyril markov.
He's a ruthless bastard.
Who's the poor bastard in our
cabinet with pancreatic cancer?
Igor and kyril markov hook you in.
we spend the next ten
years chasing a ghost.
Or it's true. and we've just got wind of it.
Emergency statement from the pm.
Given my condition. I feel I owe
it to you all to offer my resignation.
I will remain in place until
a new leader is chosen.
If a minister running for leadership
has been bribed or blackmailed.
we'd be catastrophically exposed.
Before I authorise an investigation
into any leading politician.
I'll need concrete evidence.
The mic battery's dead. Lena.
Sweet dreams?
Your little lenochka was spying on us.
And now. she's going
to tell me all her secrets.
Go back to your bed.
I'm her boss now.
Thank you.
You wanted to see me?
I'm assuming the original
intel for this Maltese op
came from cyclops?
Yes. He told me about
Igor's annual trips to Valletta.
So that information was a
plant. Everything else is. too.
It wasn't. His explanation
was entirely credible.
So you're sure of the
intelligence. What about him?
It's all in the file.
I've known him since I was
a student in st Petersburg.
And 18 years later.
he shows up in London.
working undercover at
the Russian embassy.
A senior Moscow intelligence officer
apparently looking to switch lanes.
He was already disillusioned.
Ukraine was the final straw.
You obviously kept in touch.
We stayed friends.
Were you ever lovers? No.
Did you want to be?
Not relevant. Did he?
Briefly. perhaps.
but. I was already engaged to Stuart.
So even if we'd wanted to... I see.
So it's what he might
have done but didn't
that makes you so sure of his loyalty.
A moment of weakness. perhaps...
That he chose not to take advantage of?
Isn't that worthy of trust?
We can all lie to someone we love.
And I had you down as
an incurable romantic.
This job rather beats
that out of you. I'm afraid.
You're one of our best
agent runners. Kate.
but a great desk head
requires many qualities.
Certainty isn't one of them.
So you're backing zak?
You need to find out
if your friend cyclops
has been playing you.
inadvertently or not.
Or you won't just be the
youngest head of the Russia desk.
you'll be the shortest-serving. too.
'Will you run for leadership.
foreign secretary?'
'right now. my thoughts are
just with Anthony and Jane.'
'but. foreign secretary. you've
got five days to the election.
'Don't be so coy. You need to
get a move on. really. don't you?'
'i think in a situation like this.
'it's very important to maintain
our composure as a party.'.
What did c have to
offer? Strategic ambiguity.
His speciality.
Meaning we have to prove that
we were right. or we're fucked.
And echo might be. too.
I'm gonna set up a meeting
with cyclops tomorrow morning
at the London safe house. Sure.
You need to shut that
down. Zak's in the building.
Yeah. course. but it's a
shame we can't show them this.
Come on.
That's mr Ryan Walker leaving
the NATO conference last night.
after the pm's announcement.
by the back door.
No official car. No ppos.
And no special adviser. Melissa Morris.
No. nothing. So I talked
to our Portuguese friends.
did a little triangulation.
and this was the drop-off point.
Little villa in the hills.
Guess who owns it?
Er. putin's secret mistress? Close.
Try Dmitri krimsov's brother-in-law.
Are you serious? Yeah.
So. mr Walker's response
to the resignation of our prime minister
is to go awol with the
Russian foreign minister.
Are you certain that
krimsov was at the villa?
Well. he got there half
an hour before Ryan.
Now. there was another arrival
in a taxi from the Lisbon royale.
I... I haven't ID'd him yet.
but are you ready for
the piece de resistance?
Yeah.
The man in the merc is lev amatov.
our cuddly British oligarch.
So. Ryan meets the Russian
foreign minister off-grid in a...
Hiya.
Off-grid in a get-together
brokered by a billionaire
with historic ties to the kremlin.
Well. I would call that politically suspect.
Otherwise known... as murky as fuck.
Stuart had a night out with
Melissa at the last party conference.
He said she seemed
disillusioned by working with Ryan.
I should talk to her.
We need to talk more
about this. But not here.
Sure. Do you fancy a cuppa?
Yeah.
If this leaks. Ryan's finished.
Why take the risk of going in person?
An offer he couldn't refuse.
Or maybe Ryan is the one with the ask.
On which subject.
why would Imogen accept
a 200-grand donation
from a man like lev amatov?
Well. on paper. you
could argue that he's legit.
Right? I mean. eton. Cambridge.
he's the chairman of gold scope media.
Man's a tech tycoon.
Plus. he's on the board
of the British museum
and the courtauld institute.
along with Ryan's wife.
Imogen went to this conference
in portonovi two years ago.
Stuart went.
Pretty sure he said that
lev amatov was there.
Well. there's plenty of dirty
money in Montenegro. you know.
It's a shame we can't investigate.
Assuming we follow our orders.
If zak finds out we're
working off the books...
Well. he won't. ok? Not if
we get out of his eye line.
Look. as long as you're
working on his debrief.
he's not gonna give
two shits where I am.
Anywhere in mind?
Yeah. Come on.
It's just round here.
You live so close.
Yeah. well. it means I can
wake up whenever I want to.
Come in.
Well. it's close to hq.
and it's off zak's radar.
so I'll take it.
Right. here's a spare key. Thank you.
It's my partner. Sandy's.
but he's never around. so now. it's yours.
My money is on Ryan declaring first.
Well. if Imogen goes up against him.
Stuart thinks most of
the others will back her.
All right. so let's start
with the two of them. then.
And if anyone else joins
the race. I'll go digging.
Cool? Yeah.
Five days. Better get on with it.
It's gonna be a long night.
Are you running an op in Valletta?
Malta's been put on
the alert list last night.
It came through at the embassy.
What's the alert about? I don't know.
Did you put an agent in the villa?
I need to go through your tip-off
about Igor's holidays in Valletta.
Is there any chance it could be a plant?
Is that why we're here?
You think I set you up?
Your bosses do.
The intel from my op was seismic.
much bigger than we expected.
And the chief's now
worried about blow-back.
What did you find out?
Could you have been set up?
Could anyone know we've got
ears in the villa? Not from me.
Kate. you're gonna have
to trust my judgment on this.
Unless you think I'd lie
to you? Of course I don't.
Try to find out what you can
about the red flag on Malta.
It's important. Ok.
I'll be in touch in the usual way.
'Morning.'
when did you last hear
from echo? 'Last night.'
a message saying she hadn't
changed the battery in the mic.
It's possible Moscow
knows we're watching Igor.
Fuck. How?
I don't know yet. but they've
just put Malta on the alert list.
'There was a big police bust on
gozo last night. It was on the news.
'It could be over that.' What happened?
Some fintech company
breaching Russian sanctions.
Enough to get Moscow's back up.
You know how they like to
think of this island as theirs.
'Maybe.'
but first. we need to
make sure echo's safe.
How close can you get to the villa?
Not that close.
But there's a view
from the top of the cliff.
Go there. I'll speak to Rose
about this gozo bust thing.
Don't send echo any more
messages until we've had eyes on her.
Yeah. Ok.
I know even talking about immigration
offends your metropolitan sensibilities.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
make an assumption like that.
My point is. it's... It's
not a left or a right issue.
I'm a passionate believer
in our multi-cultural society.
but it's gotta be protected.
Protected from what?
From being swamped by
uncontrolled. poorly managed.
illegal migration.
But only last week.
the home secretary said we
need migrants to do the jobs
that other people don't wanna do.
Yeah. well. even so.
we've been letting in hundreds
of thousands of people a year
for more than a decade
without building the homes.
the hospitals or anything else
we need to accommodate them.
And does that strike you two as sane?
It's going to be hard to
keep the economy moving
with zero immigration and
a higher rate of tax of 70%.
which is what you're proposing.
Yeah. on salaries over a
quarter of a million pounds.
So. obviously. it would be a
great shame to lose you both.
Sinn fein. this morning.
are calling for a referendum
on whether northern Ireland
should leave the United Kingdom.
If you become prime minister.
would you agree to that demand?
Well... perhaps it's time
we asked the English.
They pay for the union. after all.
The UK. in or out?
Foreign secretary.
is that really how you are
launching your campaign.
by playing the dog whistle
of English nationalism?
What the hell was all that about?
The right-wing press are
gonna lose their shit. Good.
Just shaking things up.
Step away from the
middle. maybe catch a wave.
Or you drown. Ryan.
We've only got four days.
You wanted to start our campaign
with a bang. Well. this is it.
The bang was supposed
to be a tough case
on pulling back on immigration.
not throwing petrol
on a nationalist bonfire.
It's an election race.
Melissa. I have to offer change.
Well. our mps are gonna hate it.
Yeah. some will. But the party
rank and file will agree with me.
more than they'd want to admit.
I get it. course I do.
But the next time you are
going disappear all night.
if you could just send me a text.
that would be great. thank you.
Sorry. Something came up.
'Well. I hope it was worth it.
'It's absolute chaos here.'
I don't know if you saw that
lunatic on gmb this morning
talking about a referendum
for the English to leave the UK.
'It's just the populist playbook.'
he can't mean it. can
he? 'Well. who knows?'
at least he's put a rocket up
Imogen's arse now he's declared.
I mean. she's still on the fence.
'Do you think anyone else will run?'
no. not if she stops
dragging her bloody heels. no.
Babe. before I forget.
you know that
conference in Montenegro.
the one you didn't wanna go to?
That was a tourist industry
junket thing. wasn't it?
Yeah. for hotels. Yeah. we
were pitching for investment.
'Why?' do you remember who set it up?
It's just the foreign office are on my back
about reviewing
ministers' security abroad.
Like I need the extra bloody admin.
'Yes. I do remember who set it up.'
it was the master of
slime himself. lev amatov.
He. er... he invited us and
sort of random backbenchers.
I mean. me and Josh told
Imogen she shouldn't bother.
but she was adamant for some reason.
'Did you get the investment?'
no. course we didn't. The only
thing I got was that food poisoning.
Remember the food poisoning I got?
Yeah. the famous squid.
'From the squid. yes.
disgusting. Please...'
I've gotta go.
Listen. don't forget. tonight.
it's Fiona's parent-teacher thing.
We are under strict instructions
to not wear anything embarrassing. ok?
I mean. as far as she's concerned.
that's impossible. Love you.
All right. Love... you too.
I spoke to gchq and Langley.
They haven't heard any
chatter coming out Malta
other than the gozo bust.
so it probably is the
reason Moscow flagged it.
"Probably" isn't enough.
We'll regroup as soon as
Julie's got a closer look at echo.
What's the news on her brother?
We've moved him to a
hostel in st Petersburg.
As soon as you pull her out.
we'll have him on his way to the border.
That's a nice brochure.
Look at the date. Look at who was there.
It was two weeks before
lev made his first donation
to Harry Conrad's charity.
Well. that's not a very
subtle quid pro quo. is it?
Exactly.
So why not declare it?
To stop the press from finding
out she's got ties to an oligarch.
It's not a very good
look for the home office.
So. are you gonna ask her about it?
I think I'll start with Angela white.
It's Julie.
What's the news? 'I can't see her.'
I've only got a limited view on the terrace.
but matti is giving sandro his breakfast.
Stay where you are
and call me the second
you see anything different.
Well. if it is what you say it is.
it would be a game-changer. wouldn't it?
No. I think we should wait.
Timing's not right at the moment. but...
Ok. Ok. yeah. thanks.
Ok. I'll call you later.
Right.
A video involving a
certain female politician's
just been brought to my attention.
Ok. What... kind of video?
We'll just have to use our imaginations.
What? A sex video of Imogen Conrad?
Shh. It sounds implausible.
but I have it on good authority.
Well. how do you know it's gonna leak?
I don't. I've just been
tipped off that it might.
By who? A journalist.
I don't know. It doesn't
matter who. does it?
We just need a strategy in case it does.
Of course. I sincerely hope it doesn't.
It'll have nothing to do
with us. will it. Ryan?
You wanted to see me?
Mrs white. I'm not sure
if you remember me.
Of course I do.
You gave no quarter to the committee.
which strikes me as a good
quality in your line of work.
Let me sign you in.
I think it's better if we
take a walk. Is that ok?
I was at the Montenegro conference
because lev asked me to be.
and I made no secret of that.
To save you the trouble. he
is a donor to my local party.
It seemed like a reasonable ask.
Did the home secretary
discuss her goals for the trip?
I barely saw her. I assumed she
was there as a favour to lev. like me.
but she didn't seem to be
taking any of it very seriously.
What do you mean by that?
She wasn't at any of the talks.
She seemed... let's put it
this way. otherwise occupied.
With what?
She spent an awful lot of time
horsing around with her aide.
There were two of them. I think.
One of them was laid
up with a tummy bug.
It was the other one.
John? Josh. Joshua long?
Good-looking chap.
Maybe there was nothing going on.
But I can't say I've
ever entirely trusted her.
Look. you're putting words in my mouth.
I didn't say I was ruling her out.
but that doesn't mean
that you can rule her in.
No. of course she isn't behind
Ryan Walker's referendum bollocks.
X? Come on. the only
thing that x is a guide to
is Elon Musk's artificially
inflated testosterone.
See you.
Can I have that for my manifesto?
We can't hold out for much longer.
We need to get out
there ahead of Ryan. ok?
I need more coffee.
What do you think I should do. love?
I always said Ryan's
smarter than he looks.
He's a wrecking ball.
And he hasn't even started on us yet.
Then you need to stop him.
Simon. hello.
Is the foreign secretary
taking mind-altering drugs?
Yes. sadly. he is a full-blown
crack addict now. Simon.
Melissa? It's Kate.
You used to work with my
husband. Stuart. at the guardian.
We met at the Christmas party.
You're the civil servant.
Home office. or was it with
mod? I actually work for sis.
We're investigating an issue
with the foreign secretary's security.
When was that? Yesterday.
We were running a routine op in Lisbon.
and we noticed he left the summit venue
without his protection officers.
I wasn't aware. No?
So there's no cause for
concern over his security detail?
Not as far as I know. no.
He went to meet lev
amatov. is that right?
A reception at a private villa.
Oddly enough. we can't
seem to find a record
of the event on the official schedule.
Well. lev's a personal
friend of the foreign secretary.
that's no secret.
What about the fact that
Dmitri krimsov was there. too?
That's a massive allegation.
You'll have to speak to the
foreign secretary about it.
I'm sure he'd be keen to
avoid a diplomatic scandal.
given the fact he's just
announced his leadership bid.
What do you expect me to do about it?
Talk to me. Melissa.
Does Ryan often go awol?
Does he shut you out of things?
He might be running the country soon.
Did Stuart tell you to come to me?
Of course not. This is between us.
I've gotta go. If you want to talk more...
In confidence. of course.
Thank fuck.
'I have eyes on her.'
she's playing cards with sandro.
sent a text saying she's fine.
'It all looks normal.'
I told you not to send
her any more messages.
'I didn't.'
then why is she answering
a question you didn't ask?
Can you send me the pictures?
I'll run back now and take a look at them.
'On it now.'
Stuart.
You all right?
Did you tell your wife.
who you forgot to mention works for sis.
what we discussed in
Manchester in confidence?
I may have mentioned something to
her about you being unhappy. yeah.
What happens at conference
stays at conference.
Isn't that the golden rule. mate?
It's nothing that anyone
couldn't have guessed. is it?
I'm sorry. though. Really. I am.
So. what. did Kate
say something to you?
I don't want things to turn dirty. Stuart.
That's not why I got into politics.
Then why are you working
for Ryan Walker. then?
How's that make sense?
He's got no business being
anyway near downing street.
and you know that. and
I know that you know.
Listen to me. Listen.
There is always room for
someone like you in our office.
I know that to be true.
I know that Imogen would
snap you up. I know it.
Just think about it.
Just have a think.
Stop. Go back one.
You see that on the edge of frame?
They're playing cards. Why
would they need security?
'I just got another text.
She's requesting a meet.'
"I hope your mum is ok. it
would be good to see her soon."
'We can see a security
guard in one of your shots.'
so?
I think she's been blown.
She's answering questions we
didn't ask her. she's being chaperoned.
and now. all of a
sudden. she wants a meet.
Ok. What next?
I'll talk to zak.
But I think I'm gonna have to go back.
You think her meet request is a set-up?
I don't know. but something feels off.
And now. we know Malta's
on the alert list as of last night.
Can you authorise a team to extract her?
It's too risky. Kate.
Best case. we'd get
you there in two days.
But we need the foreign
secretary to sign off putting weapons
through the diplomatic bag.
I don't have two days.
I'd have to go unarmed.
I can't advise that as your so.
Igor's security will be armed to the teeth.
and there might be more on the way.
I'm sorry. but the answer's no.
We've got no idea how it's
gonna go down out there.
which is exactly what
Moscow always wants.
We're just gonna have to
hope you're wrong and...
echo hasn't been blown.
I'm not leaving her there.
He made the right call.
There are too many unknowns.
I made a promise to her and alexei.
I know how much your agents
matter to you. It's why you got this job.
But you have to know when
an op goes beyond your control.
I'm not leaving her there. Rose.
Suppose zak's right. you walk into a trap.
I can handle it.
Surely. your priority
has to be... Excuse me.
Has to be protecting the Russia desk?
If any of you were
compromised out there.
it would take weeks to get
a new team up to speed.
By which time. Moscow's
asset would be in downing street.
It's a chance I'll have to take.
You take a break. ok?
Go home. see your kids.
Shit. Fiona.
Here she is. I told you she'd be here.
Nice of you to show up.
Sorry I'm late. darling. Sorry.
What have I missed?
It's the same old story.
She's got a fantastic
brain when she's focused.
But she is too easily distracted.
Wow. ok. That's
Imogen. She's... she's in.
Ok. Right. so. I'm gonna shoot off.
So we have done everything
apart from history and politics.
And this is the queue
for the a-level choices.
Stu. I'm gonna have to
work late tonight as well.
Love you. darling. Bye. Bye.
Next? Mum!
Sorry. I'm all yours. Hello.
So. do I have £8.000? 8.000.
Thank you. Eight-fifty. 9.000.
Nine. 10.000.
So. I have £10.000
for this gorgeous
Matisse lithograph. Do I...?
11.000. Thank you. sir.
12.000.
Do I have 13.000? 14.000.
Shall we round it up. mr amatov?
15.000 for such a great cause?
Sold. £15.000 to the kind gentleman.
So sorry. James. he's been held up.
Can we push it back
for 20 minutes. please?
Well. right now. he's the only candidate.
so of course he's gonna win.
Melissa thinks it'll play as
an act of toxic masculinity.
Melissa's a millennial puritan.
Trust me. anyone with ovaries
would just be bitching
about Imogen's figure.
Either way. it'd force her to pull out.
If she's got the balls
to stand against you.
But still. it's a hefty price
for her to have to pay.
I don't know how bad
this tape actually is.
If you wanna win. play
everything in your hand.
Half measures aren't
gonna get you anywhere.
So sorry to interrupt.
I have to drag him away
for the times interview.
You can do it in the car. Ok. All right.
I'll see you later. After you.
Please tell me the tip-off about the tape
didn't happen at the Lisbon party.
No. of course not. Does it exist?
Was it filmed by the
Russians? Yes. it exists.
And I told you. I've got no
idea who filmed the bloody thing
or who's in it with her.
Ok. if it's real and there's any hint
that you were behind the leak.
you know that it would sink us?
It would sink her first.
surely. Not necessarily.
A personal smear like this
could make a heroine of her.
Especially if the kremlin are behind it.
There's no evidence
of that. Doesn't matter.
The right-wing press will have a field day.
They'll say you're like one
of Moscow's fellow travellers.
like the old left.
Was lev amatov... At the Lisbon party?
He's Amanda's friend. not mine.
He's also got a Russian
passport. family ties to put in.
Yes. he's also a British citizen
who earnt his money
here fair and square.
Do you know. we're happy
enough to use his money
to prop up public spending.
He just dropped 50 grand in
there on student scholarships.
Was there anyone else
there that I should know about?
You are making a mountain
out of a molehill with this.
Ok. you took a huge risk.
I'm sure people already know
that you went off without your ppos.
Come on! What people?
There were 50 eu ministers
staying at the same hotel. Ryan.
Look. can we just leave
the cross-questioning
to the journalists. please?
I've really gotta take this!
John. hi. sorry. I'm up to my ears.
Now? You're landing this on me now?
I'm a public figure. in case
you hadn't noticed. Jesus Christ.
John. John.
No. no. no. construction was
meant to be your expertise.
offering finance was mine.
Do not get in this car until I tell you.
If mylar goes under now.
I am seriously pissed off.
Listen to me. John.
If you get fired. you better
keep your fucking mouth shut.
You can sulk all you like.
you're not spending
the weekend at Jay's.
Not after what your
teachers said tonight.
Why can't I see my boyfriend
when I'm not at school?
If you make a mistake.
Fiona... I'm not stupid.
You've known this guy for five minutes.
Have this conversation
with dad. see what he says.
Dad's not the paranoid workaholic.
I know I've been away a lot recently.
I think you like getting away from us.
It's bad timing. but I have
to go away again tomorrow.
For god's sake. I'll get the bus home.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
If you expect me to pull a million
quid out of my arse like a feather.
you have got another
fucking thing coming.
'Robert peston.' Are you alone?
'Yeah. I am.'
well. this is strictly off the record...
Here he is. monsieur Laurent sauverre.
He's a Swiss national.
I was able to track him
from krimsov's Lisbon villa
back to his hotel.
Who is he? I have no idea yet.
But the man doesn't
show up on our radar -
or anywhere else. for that matter.
Well. that tells us something.
So... you have any more
thoughts about Malta?
A few. Yeah?
We deliberately made the
approach to the church long.
So even if this meet is a set-up.
the Russians won't want
her to deviate from our plan.
which will stretch them.
And that's my chance.
What. you intercept her en route?
I've got some ideas about that. too.
Fuck. Er. yeah. I'm...
I'm gonna need a drink.
I think this is still good.
Yeah. Do you want one?
No. thanks.
Are you gonna tell Julie that
you're thinking of going rogue?
There's every chance they'll fire me. rav.
I can't do that to either of you.
Forget about the suits.
You can't do this on your own.
You should go and make
friends with your bed.
Get some rest and then decide
whether you want to throw
your entire career away.
If you stop drinking that shit now.
I'll let you know in the morning. yeah?
'Our understanding is
that with four days to go.
'the home secretary. Imogen Conrad.
'will join the leadership contest tonight.
'We're expecting her
announcement within the next...'
are you ready? Who's out there?
Everyone. Harry?
You've got this. imo.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
It is my great and timely
pleasure to announce my campaign
to be the next leader of our
party and of our great country.
'..To join the waiting press conference.
'And we need to cut
away from there now
'for some pretty sensational news
'about the other leadership candidate.
'In the last few minutes. our
political editor. Robert peston.
'has broken a bombshell
of a story. to put it mildly.
'concerning the foreign
secretary. Ryan Walker.
'The allegation. that
mr Walker slipped away
'from his personal protection team
'at the NATO summit in Lisbon this week
'and went to a party
'with the Russian foreign
minister. Dmitri krimsov.
'hosted by frequent donor
'to numerous British
political parties lev amatov.'
'this is an absolutely extraordinary story.
'Our foreign secretary. Ryan Walker.
'having a private meeting
with his Russian opposites.'
ok. we've got an hour to calm
the storm. or this race is over.
Yeah. I think you should stay quiet.
No. you shouldn't stay
quiet. They'll crucify you.
We just... we just say it was
some freelance diplomacy.
Pre-Ukraine. that might
have worked. but now?
You got any better ideas?
In this current climate.
it looks shady as hell.
Yeah. well. maybe I had no
choice but to go to that fucking party!
Yeah. well. I hope you
hang whoever leaked it.
Don't worry. I'm on it. Ok.
News at ten are asking for you.
If you come clean now.
perhaps we can salvage this.
Call bloody peston. Tell
him to get here immediately.
Too late. We won't
make the end of the show.
Well. then tell them to extend it.
Ok.
'Well. as we said. we've
extended the programme tonight
'after we were told the foreign secretary
'wanted to give us some context
'for our explosive revelations earlier.
'And I'm pleased to say Robert
is with him right now. Robert.'
thanks. Tom. Foreign secretary.
you had a private meeting.
at a Lisbon party of all things.
with the foreign minister
of Russia. a hostile state.
You were not accompanied
by any officials.
there are no notes of the meeting.
This was a clear breach of protocol.
national security has been put at risk.
Your colleagues say to
me that you should resign
and give up all ambitions
to be leader of their party.
I won't be resigning
any time soon. Robert.
Why on earth not?
In the business of diplomacy.
it's sometimes worth taking a risk.
even a personal one.
What on earth were you thinking of?
Look. it was a social gathering. right.
hosted by a very well-known
British party donor.
where Dmitri krimsov was a guest.
We shared... Did you
expect krimsov to be there?
I did expect krimsov to be there.
So why didn't you take your officials?
Well. it's not a widely publicised fact
that Dimitri krimsov lost
his only son last year.
And it's... It's fairly well-known
that my wife and I...
Sorry.
Er. we lost our only child. also a boy...
three years ago.
Sorry. And I... I wanted to express
my private sympathies to him
in the hope that we might
find some common ground.
man to man. if I'm...
if I'm allowed to say that these days.
I imagine I speak for
everybody watching.
Look. you know. obviously. I feel. for you.
enormous compassion. given
the tragedy that you suffered.
Thank you. But what do you
think you actually achieved?
How many people do you know would
be bold enough to walk in that door
and sit down with Dimitri krimsov?
How many people do you know
would try to better that
diplomatic relationship
between Europe and Russia?
I'd like you name someone in the cabinet
that you would have that confidence in.
'Thank you. Robert. Robert peston
there with the foreign secretary.'
'and that was quite some interview.
'This leadership race
is certainly hotting up.
'Let's move on to some of
the day's other news now.
'and having promised repeatedly...'
Kate.
Sorry to have summoned
you so late. mrs Henderson.
I've been on national television
fighting for my political life.
I saw. I'm sorry.
So you won't mind if I ask
you a few simple questions?
Of course.
Did you know about my
meeting with Dimitri krimsov?
Yes. How?
Some basic detective work.
I'm the foreign fucking
secretary. Your boss.
I don't need any covert surveillance!
I understand Kate had concerns
about your personal security.
Did you leak my meeting to the press?
No. Are you sure about that?
Absolutely.
Do you think I don't know
who your husband works for?
If you have a problem with my husband.
I suggest you take it up
with him. foreign secretary.
or Imogen herself.
But you'll admit you don't
like my politics. do you?
I'm a civil servant.
Your politics are none of my business.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell us. Kate?
No. Unless mr Walker would?
Do you think I would take
the trouble to come here
if I'd done anything underhand?
It's not my job to say. sir.
My job is to help keep you safe.
If we've failed to do that here at sis.
then I'm sure I speak for everyone
when I say it is deeply regrettable.
Well. if you've no more
questions. foreign secretary...
Take this as an official warning.
Do not meddle with
the Democratic process.
Hiya.
Hi. Did you see it?
What a fucking night. Front-row seat.
I mean. Meg's already
asked for his resignation.
He's cooked. He's done.
Well. I think it's gonna take
more than this to kill him off.
I mean. maybe. but. it now means
that Imogen is officially
in the fucking race.
Can I ask you something? Yeah.
Do you think Imogen's
ever been unfaithful?
What. to Harry?
I mean. no. not that I know of. Why?
Forget it.
Katie. if you've heard
something about her.
I could really do with knowing. you know.
Especially given she's now declared. No.
Forget about it. I just
wanted your opinion. All right.
Are you ok? You had a rough night?
I've had better.
Anything you can talk about. or...?
I was accused of passing intel
about the krimsov meeting to you.
To me?
Well. who's accused you? Zak?
Man of the moment. Ryan Walker.
I mean. honestly. do they
think we'd be that fucking stupid?
Apparently so.
Did you know. though...
about Ryan meeting krimsov?
I mean. is that what that trip was about?
I can't talk about it.
You can't talk about it.
Given the fact that you're
investigating him... we're not.
And that's it. Stuart. I
can't talk about it. All right.
Sorry.
Well...
Bloody hell. well. we'd
better win. then. hey?
I'm a civil servant. I can't comment. Yes.
Your neutrality is noted. as ever.
I'm not joking. Stuart. I'm not joking.
I'm really sorry. but I have
to go away again tomorrow.
I'll be gone before you're up. though.
Ok. What? You... What. is
it something serious. or...?
It's a potentially hostile environment.
'Everything is in place.
'Now you are going to find
out what Henderson knows.'
Malta is not the best place to die.
Don't be stupid.
Confirm the meeting in
the church this morning.
Now.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com